esyndicat.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy :: eSyndiCat Directory Software, Directory Script, Business Directory Software, Link Bid Script

## Customer Privacy

eSyndiCat respects your privacy. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of eSyndiCat.

Remember the risks whenever you use the Internet. While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to eSyndiCat and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through eSyndiCat have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. 

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

## External Sites

eSyndiCat is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

## Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows eSyndiCat to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and eSyndiCat does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

 Cookie |  Developer |  Description |  Expiration  
---|---|---|---  
 __utma |  Google Analytics |  Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics. |  2 Years.  
 __utmb |  Google Analytics |  Used to determine new sessions/visits. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utmb cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics. |  30 mins from set/update.  
 __utmc |  Google Analytics |  Not used in ga.js. Set for interoperability with urchin.js. Historically, this cookie operated in conjunction with the __utmb cookie to determine whether the user was in a new session/visit. |  End of browser session.  
 __utmt |  Google Analytics |  Used to throttle request rate. |  10 minutes.  
 __utmz |  Google Analytics |  Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics. |  6 months.  
 _ZB_ADMIN_LAST_URL |  Zotabox |  Checking for the last URL visited by the user. |  1 year.  
 _ZB_ADMIN_TIME_STAMP_ |  Zotabox |  Checking the time stamp. |  1 year.  
 _ZB_STATIC_DR_currentSessionTimeVisit |  Zotabox |  Checking current session time visit. |  1 year.  
 _ZB_STATIC_DR_firstTimeVisit |  Zotabox |  Checking if this is your first time on Esyndicat.com |  1 year.  
 _ZB_STATIC_DR_isEU |  Zotabox |  Checking if your located within the European Union so it can display the Cookie LAW agreement. |  1 year.  
 _ZB_STATIC_DR_widgetsUpdateTime |  Zotabox |  Stores the active time spend on the site and based on this display neseccary popups. |  1 year.  
 _ZB_STATS_IMPRESSION_PREMIUM |  Zotabox |  Checking for available Zotabox impressions left. |  1 year.  
 _ZB_STATS_IMPRESSION.5ba93903 |  Zotabox |  Stores every impression to the site. |  1 year.  
 _ZB_STATS_VISIT |  Zotabox |  Stores the follow statistics from visitor: Location, IP, Browser, Operating System, Javascript if enabled, Time spend on Site and other analytic data. |  1 year.  
 PHPSESSID |  PHP |  The PHPSESSID cookie is native to PHP and enables websites to store serialised state data. On the Action website it is used to establish a user session and to pass state data via a temporary cookie, which is commonly referred to as a session cookie. As the PHPSESSID cookie has no timed expiry, it disappears when the client is closed. |  Ends when you quit from your browser.  
  
#### How can I disable cookies and manage my preferences ? 

The majority of browsers are configured to accept, control or potentially disable cookies through the settings. We nevertheless remind you that disabling navigation or functional cookies may affect the functioning of the website and/or limit the service we offer.   
It is possible to browse and temporarily prevent the browser from recording cookies by using the incognito mode or a private browsing mode: 

Below is the procedure to follow to manage cookies from the following browsers: 

For more information on cookies and to manage your preferences for third party profiling cookies, please go to 

To disable analytical cookies and prevent Google Analytics from collecting data on your navigation, you can download the add-on from your browser to deactivate Google Analytics: 

. 

For more information and details about the various types of cookies, their mode of operation and features, please visit 

, 

## Report Piracy URL

Please send an email to manager@esyndicat.com if you suspect a site is not using a valid license of eSyndiCat or if they are breaking the [license agreement](http://www.esyndicat.com/license.html). We take piracy very seriously, and appreciate your help in our efforts to reduce any piracy or illegal distribution of our software.

Alternatively you can report piracy using our [contact form](http://www.esyndicat.com/contact-us.html?piracy=true).
